----------------------------------------------
Readme - Current Version (v1.5)
         For ArmA3. Released - 8/26/2015
----------------------------------------------

------
Legal
------

This Addon is only to be used for ArmA3 and official ArmA3 expansion packs.
Any unauthorised use or editing of this Addon is against the EULA & is NOT allowed.
You could be prosecuted if you break any of these rules. 

Please respect Addon makers and do NOT edit their work!.
Thank you!

I take no responsibility for (im)possible damage to your game/system that may be caused by installation of this Addon.

-------------------
Use of the MH-47E's
-------------------

The MH-47E's can be found under 'BLUFOR' > 'NATO' > 'Air'.
The 2 MH-47E's damaged wreck's can be found under 'Empty' > 'Wrecks' & 'Wrecks (Submerged)'.

Only to be used in ArmA3 + ArmA3 Expansion Packs.

---------
Features
---------

• Compatible with AGM Fast Roping.
• Firing From Vehicle, For Both Ramp Positions. (Fixed Ramp Version Only)
• Ability to Slingload Using BIS's New Feature. (Heli DLC).
• Correct Number of Flares/Countermeasures in a Forward Direction.
• Lock Dectection System Complete with Warning Sounds.
• Walkable Fuselarge.
• Digital Cockpit for Pilot & Co-Pilot.
• Pilot & Co-Pilot's Collective & Cyclic work with the Chinook's movement.
• Option to Level, Lower & Raise Ramp.
• 2 Cargo Positons on the Edge of the Ramp. (Fixed Ramp Version Only)
• New & Improved Flight Engine Sound's.
• 19 Different Radio Chatter Sounds.
• Improved Blade System, bend when under load etc.
• Custom Cargo Positions. (BackCrew & Loadmaster)
• Compatible with "Lala14's" Interior Lighting Script.
• Co-Pilot Camera is fully animated.
• FLIR & Laser Marker on Co-Pilots Camera.
• Animated Loadmasters Hatch.
• Animated Windscreen Wipers.
• Ability to load an ATV or CRRC via tryteyker's script.
• Ability to Sling Load Vehicle's & Ammo. (See Raven LIFTER).
• Fast Roping for Cargo Crew Passengers.(See Raven LIFTER).
• A "Hardcore" Version, Where You Disembark From Inside The MH-47E.
• 2 Wreckage Models.
• Signed AddOn for online use.

-----------------------------
Detailed Feature Instructions
-----------------------------

• To display a texture of your own onto the flag in the cargo area, simply do the following below.
  Simply edit a flag or logo of your choice into the white space in the FlagTextureTemplate.png file included in the zip folder.
  Once done, save the image into your mission file as a .paa file format, and in the MH-47E init's field ingame put the following:

  this setObjectTexture [0,"YourTextureName.paa"];

  Then, once mission is loaded and saved, you will see the flag of your choice.

• To use the Fast Roping, Sling Loading of Vehicles & Ammo thats compatiable with this AddOn.
  Please refer to Raven's LIFTER for ArmA3 on BIS Forums.

• To load either an ATV or a CRRC into the Chinook. Please refer to tryteyker ATV/CRRC Readme file, located in the .zip archive of this download.

------------
Class Names
------------

• kyo_MH47E_base - Standard MH-47E.

  * The Normal version is same as the 'Hardcore' version but with the get out positions on the outside of the Chinook so the AI aren't stuck inside it.

• kyo_MH47E_Ramp - MH-47E with Fixed Ramp.
  
  * The Fixed Ramp version of the MH-47E has the ramp fixed at the 'Level Ramp' position as there is extra spaces on the ramp for 2 men to sit on the 
    edge of the ramp.

• kyo_MH47E_HC - The 'HardCore' Version.

  * The 'Hardcore' version is strictly for Multiplayer really (Intended to anyway). As all the get out positions are inside the Chinook, so therefor you
    can exit the chopper and run out the ramp on a cliff extraction or sea extraction etc.

• kyo_CH47_HC3 - RAF CH-47 HC.3.

  * RAF version of the CH-47 HC.3 Chinook.

----------------
Credit & Thanks
----------------

I would like to thank the following people below, everyone mentioned below has been apart of the Chinook from the start.
Although I dont know them or what they done to help this Chinook as It was done before my time i started with it. I'd still like to thank them all.
So thanks to...

 Afrographx, Smiley_Nick, The Spanish Mod Team, UOE.Txalo, TF86 Ardvark, TF86 Mac, SwissMAG, All the TF86 Crew, Sickboy, PvPscene, Pelton, Eddie(Wld427), 
 Deanobeano, Topas, Marrius & TCBRUNCH.

There proabably were some more people included who helped with the Chinook from its birth, the list above dosen't seem big enough from it's time.
Most likly lost in communiction and the model changing over hands. so If anyone should be included above, that isan't. Please let me know! Thank you.

Also again I would like to thank the following people below. Since I've had the Chinook the people below have helped me countless times to iron out
errors, without all these great below & above.. The Chinook wouldnt be as great as it is. So thanks! :D  

 Sv5000 for helping with adding FLIR to the co-pilots camera, RKSL-Rock also for help with FLIR camera,
 Norrin for the original fast roping & slingloading scripts for ArmA & ArmA2, Cards525 - Khaki & all at sfod-delta, Deadfast for the window wipers scripts,
 BlackMamb for the original Radio Chatter script for ArmA2, Shadow [MSOAR] for updating the Radio Chatter script & Simulation usage class, 
 astast for the burnt engine fire texture in the wreck model, Myke for help fixing the Useractions Menu, Ei8ght for pre-release ACE testing for ArmA2,
 Sakura_Chan for the improved Gunner Animations in ArmA2, soldier2390 for the example mission's - SOAR pilots & the new re-texture,
 w0lle for help changing Get in co-pilot from Get in Gunner, VXR for his amazing help at detailing and weathering the textures,
 tryteyker for his brilliant ATV loading script for ArmA2 & ArmA3, Soul Assisin for animation and config tips, Franze for help with fixing altitude reading
 0 error, islesfan186 for suggesting to talk to Franze to fix that error, SwissMag for fixing the Rotor alignment & HUD display. Slatts for Slingload
 advice. DeltaGamer for his willingness to help me on many issues.

But.. Last but not least, I'd like to thank YuraPetrov for his countless help & my silly questions I kept.. & well lets be honest, still keep asking him.
Without Yura, this helicopter really wouldnt be here. So thank you so much Yura, I owe you a few beers mate! спасибо Yura! :D 
  
---------------
Contact Details
---------------

Fill in a Contact form on www.konyo.webs.com
Or Email me at : konyo.webs@googlemail.com

=================== Disclaimer: ========================
This is NOT an official Addon. Use it at your own risk.
========================================================